<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>example on luigi cennini</title>
    <link>/en/tags/example/</link>
    <description>Recent content in example on luigi cennini</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 19:53:33 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/en/tags/example/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bézier curves and patches - interactive visualization</title>
      <link>/en/projects/bezier/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 19:53:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/projects/bezier/</guid>
      <description>Bézier Curves Bézier curves are a fundamental concept in computer graphics and vector drawing. They are used to describe curves by controlling points called &amp;lsquo;control points&amp;rsquo;. These curves were introduced by Pierre Bézier in the 1960s as a method of representing curves on computer screens. A Bézier curve has the form
$$\underline{x}(t) = \sum_{i=0}^n \underline{b}_i B_i^n(t), t\in[0,1]$$
Where,
$$B_i^n(t) = {n \choose i}t^i(1-t)^{n-i}, i= 0,&amp;hellip;,n$$
are the n+1 basic Bernstein polynomials.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>fork telemetry</title>
      <link>/en/projects/fork-telemetry/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 19:53:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/projects/fork-telemetry/</guid>
      <description>Introduction The aim of this project is to develop a cheaper alternative to the telemetry systems available on the market for mountain bikes.
Telemetry systems for mountain bikes monitor and acquire data on the position of the bike&amp;rsquo;s fork and shock absorber while riding. This data is crucial for off-road sports enthusiasts and professional athletes, as it provides valuable information for analysing and improving performance.
Currently, many telemetry systems, such as byb telemetry, use expensive linear potentiometers to accurately measure the position of the fork and shock absorber.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>graph theory visualizer</title>
      <link>/en/projects/graph-theory-visualizer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 19:53:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/projects/graph-theory-visualizer/</guid>
      <description>graphTheory-Visualizer The project was done to visualize the operations that can be done on a graph, such as BFS, DFS, Kruskal, and Dijkstra.
The goal is to have a real time update of the various operations, so that if the graph changes while an &amp;lsquo;operation is being performed on it, the result of the operation also changes.
The project is active on GitHub pages and a demo can be accessed from this link: https://giggiox.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
